

# +55 21 98054-0128 ux.emerson@gmail.com

#### **INFO**

Hello, my name is Emerson. I'm from Rio de Janeiro, and I've been working in Design since 2009, aiming to create harmony between people and businesses to deliver the right solution for the right problem with quality and efficiency.

Linkedin e Behance

#### **EXPERTISE**

# Metodologias

- Design Thinking
- Design Sprint
- Scrum

## **User Interface Guidelines**

- Google Material Design
- Apple Human Interface Guidelines
- Design System

# **Prototipagem**

- Figma / Sketch / Adobe XD / Webflow
- MarvelApp / InvisionApp / Maze
- HTML / CSS / JavaScript
- Design Responsivo / Desktop / Mobile

### **Testes**

- Exploratory
- Usability
- Performance

# Análise

- Google Analytics
- Hotjar

Portfolio emersonalmeida.github.io

## **EXPERIENCE**

2021 - 2022

Grupo SOMA

Product Designer

2018 - 2019

VML - Oi

**UX/UI Designer** 

2017

**Ydreams** 

**UI** Designer

2016

**WPensar** 

**UX/UI Designer** 

2014-2015

MundiPagg

**UX/UI Designer** 

2010 - 2013

**B2W - Americanas.com** 

**UX/UI** Designer

2009

**6D Studio** 

Web Designer

# **FORMAÇÃO**

2022

Meiuca - Design System

Curso

2005 - 2008

SENAI - Produção Gráfica

Técnico

Linkedin

linkedin.com/in/emersonalmeidadesigner